<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle"  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>TeXnicle's Changelog</title>
		<link>http://www.bobsoft-mac.de/texnicle_appcast.xml</link>
		<description>Most recent changes with links to updates.</description>
		<language>en</language>

    
    <!-- Version 2.0 beta 48 -->
		<item>
      <title>Version 2.0 (beta 48)</title>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>
        This fixes a minor bugs and one big one associated with saving new stand-alone TeX files.
        </p>
        <p>
      ]]></description>
      <pubDate>22nd July 2012</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="http://www.bobsoft-mac.de/resources/TeXnicle/Beta/TeXnicle.app.beta48.zip"
      sparkle:shortVersionString="2.0"
      sparkle:version="48"
      length="15466322"
      type="application/octet-stream"
      sparkle:dsaSignature="MCwCFAIje8U3nJCTHjfE1klHzD9uy1VaAhRHSDEGCLOuKHNz3rAHhrpFnpmyeQ=="
      />
    </item>
    
		<!-- Version 2.0 beta 47 -->
		<item>
       <title>Version 2.0 (beta 47)</title>
       <description><![CDATA[
         <p>
         This will be the last beta release with feature changes. The plan is for one (or possibly two) more beta
         release focussing on any reported bugs before releasing the final version of TeXnicle 2.0. Further change
         requests will be looked at in the development of version 2.1.
         </p>
         <p>
         A Significant amount of behind-the-scenes changes have taken place in this release, so it is recommended
         that you have a good backup of any files (including TeXnicle's preferences file found under
         ~/Library/Preferences/com.bobsoft.TeXnicle.plist) before using this version. No problems are expected,
         but you never know.
         </p>
         <h3>Focus Area: Spell Checking</h3>
         <p>
         TeXnicle has two new features associated with spell checking. The first is that the dictionary language
         can be specified for individual documents or projects. This is done on the project/document settings tab.
         </p>
         <p>
         The second is a project-wide spelling list which appears as a new navigation pane on projects. This
         shows a list of project files and misspelled words within them.
         </p>
         <p>
         You can correct words directly from the spelling pane using the "Correct" action button, or using the
         context menu of the listed words. You can also jump to the misspelled word in the editor by double
         clicking on the word in the list or by clicking the "Reveal" button.
         </p>
         <p>
         Files are checked every 1s, but only if there have been changes since the last check. You can force a
         full check of all files by clicking the "Force Check" button. The spell checking is only done for file
         types which are listed in the "File Types" preference pane and which have Spell Check selected.
         </p>
         <p>
         It is recommended to install CocoaASpell from http://cocoaspell.leuski.net/. This provides
         system-wide dictionaries which are TeX aware. The following article is a useful
         read: http://www.jkwchui.com/2010/03/spellchecking-latex-in-macosx/.
         </p>
         <p>
         <h3>Other Changes</h3>
         <ul>
         <li>New spelling panel for projects (see release notes).</li>
         <li>The spelling dictionary language can now be specified per project or document (see release notes).</li>
         <li>It is now possible to control the depth of the outline that's shown in the outline view.</li>
         <li>Added a preference to activate/deactivate restoring open tabs in projects.</li>
         <li>Added a preference to control the interval between live updates.</li>
         <li>Added two new menu items under view to show the integrated console and pdf viewer should they be collapsed.</li>
         <li>Added 3 new syntax highlighting elements which 'markup' the text between < >, << >>, or <<< >>>. Useful for
         marking text that needs to be edited later. These elements are off by default.</li>
         <li>Project searching can now be restricted to case sensitive or whole word searches.</li>
         <li>PDF viewer now displays the current page number and total page count.</li>
         <li>Bug fix: added a workaround for the bug in 10.7.4 which stops PDFs being displayed properly.</li>
         <li>Bug fix: project search results remain valid even after the content of the files changes.</li>
         <li>Bug fix: selecting rearranged tabs could result in crashing.</li>
         <li>Various bug fixes and optimisations, especially to the underlying project document management.</li>
         </ul>
         </p>
       ]]></description>
       <pubDate>21st July 2012</pubDate>
       <enclosure url="http://www.bobsoft-mac.de/resources/TeXnicle/Beta/TeXnicle.app.beta47.zip"
       sparkle:shortVersionString="2.0"
       sparkle:version="47"
       length="22712320"
       type="application/octet-stream"
      sparkle:dsaSignature="MEQCIHA4jFYOa8xBzrtS+CNSQdbzMi0FWjAqR/H6kcRZjVDhAiBAx1tnJwg+uL6ZnaGbyFco1wLBMEtPqqozsg9OAwUdyA=="
       />
     </item>

     
		<!-- Version 2.0 beta 46 -->
		<item>
            <title>Version 2.0 (beta 46)</title>
            <description><![CDATA[
              <h2>New features</h2>
              <ul>
                <li>Added a syntax highlighting element for $ characters.</li>
                <li>Added new 'Navigators' menu under 'View' which allows switching between the various
                    navigators, and showing the left panel when it's collapsed.</li>
                <li>Added a preference on the Typesetting preference pane to clear consoles on typesetting.</li>
                <li>Project tabs are now reopened in the order in which they were when the project was closed.</li>
              </ul>
              <h2>Bug fixes</h2>
              <ul>
                <li>Automatically adding \end after \begin now works even if some text follows the \begin{} statement.</li>
                <li>Saving projects after rearranging editor tabs sometimes caused a crash. This is fixed now.</li>
                <li>Various other minor bug fixes.</li>
              </ul>
            ]]></description>
            <pubDate>23 June 2012</pubDate>
            <enclosure	url="http://www.bobsoft-mac.de/resources/TeXnicle/Beta/TeXnicle.app.beta46.zip"
                        sparkle:shortVersionString="2.0"
                        sparkle:version="46"
                        length="1472893"
                        type="application/octet-stream"
                        sparkle:dsaSignature="MEQCIFx8ciNg934w0ArQskwPvuWY+h+mNl7vM8xbR49QUPGxAiAIveR1fQI96FGOsrGvBqIMEt3i/t57cHdVWkwe8EA+2g=="
            />
         </item>

   </channel>
</rss>